<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Work Experience on Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/categories/work-experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work Experience on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>James Barowik</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/categories/work-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Medical Work Experience</title>
      <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/brandon-medical/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/brandon-medical/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:Over the last 3 months, I have been fortunate enough to have completed 45 days work experience required to complete the Digital T-Level at UTC Leeds, the work placement is a key part of the Digital T-Level, well the T-Level in general to ensure that you are able to gain experience in the sector that you are planning on working in.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartsearch Game</title>
      <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/smartsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/smartsearch/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:Smartsearch approached the UTC with an idea that they wanted to make a game to showcase there company at events. We initial met with them in person and spoke with Dan that was our a lead contact at Smartsearch and the team. We also met with David who is one of the software developers at SmartSearch he assisted along the way with more of the team management to ensure that we were on the right tracks and that we made a viable product at the end that could be used to bring people to the SmartSearch stand and get them interetsed.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundo Work Experience</title>
      <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/hundo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/hundo/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:As part of the Digital T-Level we are required to complete a minmum of 45 days work experience. For this project we worked with Leeds City Council and Hundo
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
