<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/categories/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>James Barowik</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/categories/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Silent Debian Script</title>
      <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/silent-debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/silent-debian/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:I had wanted to learn linux for the longest time but never really got the opportunity as in a learning situation Windows was the operating system that was used, then same for the work placement. Which ment I got really comfortable using the Windows operating system.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi Bash Project</title>
      <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/rpi5-bash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/rpi5-bash/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:To further my career and learning, and the installation of the Raspberry Pi Cluster. I looked into creating a bash script, that would automate the process as much as possible to reduce the amount of time that it took to setup and install all of the machines. Something that I would like to look into in the future is the addition of a deployment server that install the OS automatically across the network of machines. I currently have no idea how I’d go about doing that so using a bash based automated process.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox</title>
      <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/proxmox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/proxmox/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:Firstly, we installed Windows Server 2019 on the bare metal. As I wanted to learn more skills related to infrastructure it was essential that I could learn linux skills as well as windows skills. So, I spent a few days looking around at other solutions that ment I was able to learn more with the hardware and I stumbled across Proxmox.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrueNAS Scale</title>
      <link>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/truenas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barowik-portfolio.netlify.app/truenas/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:We needed a safe fast and secure solution for storage. We need a solution that supported both Windows Shares (SMB) and Linux Shares. With the requirements that we need and the hardware that we have the search began. For the OS that was compatible with our older hardware and that worked with never drives that were harvested from our old college machines that were no longer in use.
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
